Guide to the Robert Giard Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- February 2005 Acquisition, 1972-2002; 1; 50.06; (270 boxes)
  - Oversize Photographs (16" x 20")
    - Landscapes
      - Gay Sites
        - (Homomonuments sign, canal-Amsterdam), undated (Box 246)
          GS# 0102
        - (Homomonument sign, boat, canal, figure at right-Amsterdam), undated (Box 246)
          GS# 0103
    - Portraits
      - Children
        - (teenage boy in dark turtleneck), undated (Box 246)
          P# 0145a
        - (two teenage boys-see 0145a and 0146a), undated (Box 246)
          P# 0146a
        - (teenage boy in polo shirt), undated (Box 247)
          P# 0147a
        - (boy seated in chair in corner of room), undated (Box 247)
          P# 0148a
        - (three children on blanket in front of tree), undated (Box 247)
          P# 0149b
        - Miles Hirschberg (baby in overalls), undated (Box 247)
          P# 0150b
        - Ann Silin (smiling), undated (Box 247)
          P# 0151
        - Ann Silin, undated (Box 247)
          P# 0152c
        - Daisy Klingman, undated (Box 247)
          P# 0153b
        - Child in a Ballet Costume (Daisy Klingman), 1980 (Box 247)
          P# 0154
        - Daisy Klingman, 1981 (Box 247)
          P# 0155c
        - Daisy Klingman (with photographs by Robert Giard), undated (Box 247)
          P# 0156c
        - (three children seated on bench with arms raised, undated (Box 247)
          P# 0158c
        - (two seated girls, one with stuffed animals), undated (Box 247)
          P# 0158b
      - Mixed Group
        - (couple in formal attire posed outside), undated (Box 247)
          P# 0159
        - (couple posed on front porch), undated (Box 247)
          P# 0160
        - Artist and Model (David Julin and Claudia), 1982 (Box 247)
          P# 0161b
        - Skinner Family, undated (Box 247)
          P# 0162a
        - Elizabeth and Robert Skinner, undated (Box 247)
          P# 0163a
        - (dining al fresco), undated (Box 247)
          P# 0164a
        - (couple posed in front of bamboo), undated (Box 247)
          P# 0165
        - (family of four posed in front of china cabinet), undated (Box 247)
          P# 0166b
        - Harold Snedcoff and his wife, undated (Box 248)
          P# 0167a
        - Snedcoff parents, undated (Box 248)
          P# 0168
        - Allen Ellenzweig's sister and family, undated (Box 248)
          P# 0169
        - (two men, two boys seated at table- owners- Garth Clark Gallery, NYC), undated (Box 248)
          P# 0170a
        - (two men, one with mustache), undated (Box 248)
          P# 0171c
        - Bill Burns and companion, undated (Box 248)
          P# 0172c
        - Couple with Children, NYC, 1990 (Box 248)
          P# 0173b
        - (male couple in suits-owners of Garth Clark Gallery, NYC), undated (Box 248)
          P# 0174
        - (male couple in polo shirts-owners of Garth Clark Gallery, NYC-see 0174), undated (Box 248)
          P# 0175
      - Self-Portraits
        - Self Portrait (after Nadar's George Sand), 1977 (Box 248)
          P# 0176
        - (nude in bathroom mirror), undated (Box 248)
          P# 0177a
        - (posed against concrete block wall with ivy wreath crown), undated (Box 248)
          P# 0178
      - Male
        - (male in tuxedo, portrait painting in background, unidentified), undated (Box 248)
          P# 0001a
        - Man with a Cigar (Jim Anderson - painter), 1980 (Box 248)
          P# 0002g
        - Portrait of Swami Bua, 1984 (Box 248)
          P# 0003a
        - Man with Scorpio Statue (Robert Benzio), 1981 (Box 248)
          P# 0004
        - Man with a Telescope (Peter Solaski), 1980 (Box 248)
          P# 0005c
        - Portrait of Erte, 1980 (Box 248)
          P# 0006b
        - Head and Carafe (Joseph Durso - designer), 1977 (Box 248)
          P# 0007b
        - Man in a Short-Sleeved Shirt, 1984 (Box 248)
          P# 0008c
        - Man on a Pillow (Gerald Busby-composer, actor), 1981 (Box 249)
          P# 0009c
        - Man with a Mug (Frederick Rostock), 1979 (Box 249)
          P# 0010c
        - Man in a Neck Brace (Tommy Burns), 1980 (Box 249)
          P# 0011
        - Portrait of Bruce Cratsley - photographer, 1988 (Box 249)
          P# 0012A
        - Portrait of Bruce Cratsley (profile) - photographer, 1988 (Box 249)
          P# 0013a
        - Man in a Hooded Sweat Shirt (Arthur Tress - photographer), 1977 (Box 249)
          P# 0014c
        - (man reclining in robe-John Dryer), undated (Box 249)
          P# 0015
        - (man seated on stairway), undated (Box 249)
          P# 0016
        - (man in jumpsuit), undated (Box 249)
          P# 0017
        - (man posed in front of ledge with bottled-Michael Hampton), undated (Box 249)
          P# 0018c
        - Man Holding a Lamp (William Wilson - editor), 1979 (Box 249)
          P# 0019a
        - Man in a Suit (Barry Klingman), 1980 (Box 249)
          P# 0020
        - Artist with Painting (Riccardo Wiesenberg), 1981 (Box 249)
          P# 0021c
        - Portrait of Michael Graves-architect, 1979 (Box 249)
          P# 0022b
        - Michael Graves (full length)-architect, 1979 (Box 249)
          P# 0023c
        - (man holding St. Bernard-Arthur Trifari), undated (Box 249)
          P# 0024a
        - (seated man, pillar at right, close-up - unidentified painter), undated (Box 249)
          P# 0025b
        - (seated man, pillar at right - unidentified painter), undated (Box 249)
          P# 0026c
          See 0025b
        - (man leaning against pillar, dog at feet - unidentified painter), undated (Box 249)
          P# 0027b
        - (man posed between stairway and door), undated (Box 249)
          P# 0028
        - Boy on a Unicycle (Anton Hart), 1977 (Box 250)
          P# 0029b
        - (man in sweater and hat-Charlie Phillips), undated (Box 250)
          P# 0030c
        - Man Behind a Window (Joseph Durso- designer), 1977 (Box 250)
          P# 0031b
        - (seated man in striped necktie-Harold Snedcoff), undated (Box 250)
          P# 0032a
        - Man with Trompe L'Oeil (Peter Carlson -editor at Architectural Digest/GQ), 1976 (Box 250)
          P# 0033a
        - Man in a Horned Chair (Sydney Butcher -artist), 1978 (Box 250)
          P# 0034a
        - (portrait of man, statues at left -unidentified), undated (Box 250)
          P# 0035a
        - [unidentified], undated (Box 250)
          P# 0037
        - Man in Bed (Jonathan Silin), 1977 (Box 250)
          P# 0037a
        - (portrait of man in overcoat and hat-unidentified), 1984 (Box 250)
          P# 0038b
        - (man in t-shirt seated on stairs, close-up - Peter), 1986 (Box 250)
          P# 0039b
        - (man in t-shirt seated on stairs - Peter), 1986 (Box 250)
          P# 0040c
        - Newton McMahon-artist, 1981 (Box 250)
          P# 0041c
      - Female
        - (woman with melon rind-Christianne Drabbe), undated (Box 250)
          P# 0042b
        - (woman eating melon slice-Christianne Drabbe), undated (Box 250)
          P# 0043b
        - Young Woman with Natural Hair (Elizabeth Spinzia), 1981 (Box 250)
          P# 0044a
        - (portrait of woman in peasant garb -Nadja Tassich [sp?]-writer), 1984 (Box 250)
          P# 0045c
        - Woman by a Window (Nadia Gould), 1980 (Box 250)
          P# 0046a
        - Woman at a Door (Ann Ryden), 1984 (Box 250)
          P# 0047c
        - (portrait of a woman, 1/4 view-Victoria Burns), 1983 (Box 250)
          P# 0048c
        - (back of a woman in lace top), 1979 (Box 251)
          P# 0049b
        - (portrait of woman holding watermelon slice-Susan Raymond), 1983 (Box 251)
          P# 0050c
        - Woman Sunning (Marge Caggiano), 1978 (Box 251)
          P# 0051b
        - Muriel Dimen (hands on chest), writer, psychoanalyst, undated (Box 251)
          P# 0052
        - Muriel Dimen (head resting on hand), writer, psychoanalyst, undated (Box 251)
          P# 0053a
        - Woman with a Snood (Irma Brownfield), 1978 (Box 251)
          P# 0054a
        - Woman Holding a Photograph of Her Father (Mimi Black), 1979 (Box 251)
          P# 0055a
        - Woman with Her Hair in a Towel (Arlene Klingman), 1979 (Box 251)
          P# 0056a
        - (portrait of a woman in dark top), undated (Box 251)
          P# 0057a
        - (woman reciting, dog at feet), undated (Box 251)
          P# 0058
          Related Archival Materials note
          See PF0096g
        - (woman wrapped in rug), undated (Box 251)
          P# 0059a
        - (woman wrapped in rug, profile), undated (Box 251)
          P# 0060c
        - Muriel Dimen (hand near face), writer, psychoanalyst, undated (Box 251)
          P# 0061a
        - Lisa Vahradian (seated next to doll house), opera singer, undated (Box 251)
          P# 0062
        - Lisa Hirschberg, artist, undated (Box 251)
          P# 0063
        - Judith Levine, writer, 1983 (Box 251)
          P# 0064c
        - Woman with an Accordion (Joyce Culver, photographer), 1980 (Box 251)
          P# 0065a
        - (woman holding lorgnette- Irene Gould), 1980 (Box 251)
          P# 0066d
        - Woman with a Lorgnette (Irene Gould), 1980 (Box 251)
          P# 0067
        - Woman with Wicker Furniture (Diane Lindley), 1978 (Box 251)
          P# 0068a
        - (profile portrait, seated woman -unidentified), undated (Box 252)
          P# 0069
        - (portrait of a woman-Ms. Snedcoff), undated (Box 252)
          P# 0070
        - Mary Peterson-college dean, undated (Box 252)
          P# 0071d
        - Hanna Brencken, artist, undated (Box 252)
          P# 0072c
    - Portraits-Figures-Landscape/Work
      - Model At Rest, 1981 (Box 252)
        PF# 0073c
      - (man beating rug), 1983 (Box 252)
        PF# 0074b
      - (man trimming hedges), 1979 (Box 252)
        PF# 0075d
      - (two men erecting tent), undated (Box 252)
        PF# 0076c
      - (man painting porch roof), 1979 (Box 252)
        PF# 0077d
      - (woman holding up crocheted spread), undated (Box 252)
        PF# 0078d
      - (man posed with rake), undated (Box 252)
        PF# 0079c
      - (man posed with rake-head turned to profile), undated (Box 252)
        PF# 0080b
      - (man fertilizing or seeding lawn), undated (Box 252)
        PF# 0081c
      - Nurse, 1981 (Box 252)
        PF# 0082d
      - (man in white coveralls), undated (Box 252)
        PF# 0083d
      - (man using leaf blower), undated (Box 252)
        PF# 0084d
      - Man with Fishes, 1978 (Box 252)
        PF# 0085b
      - Two Men Searching for Money, 1984 (Box 252)
        PF# 0086c
      - Woman Raking Leaves, 1983 (Box 252)
        PF# 0087d
      - (figure standing behind leafing vine), 1979 (Box 252)
        PF# 0088d
      - (woman at melon stand), 1983 (Box 253)
        PF# 0089d
      - (seated vendor at outdoor flea market), undated (Box 253)
        PF# 0090d
      - (man checking under hood of car with "stethoscope"), undated (Box 253)
        PF# 0091d
      - Portrait of My Father, undated (Box 253)
        PF# 0092a
      - Man in Tuxedo, undated (Box 253)
        PF# 0093a
      - Swami, 1983 (Box 253)
        PF# 0094d
      - Baby on a Blanket, 1983 (Box 253)
        PF# 0095a
      - Woman Reading Poetry Aloud (a.k.a. Poet Reading Aloud-see P0058), 1985 (Box 253)
        PF# 0096g
      - (woman squatting with three dogs), undated (Box 253)
        PF# 0097a
      - (three dogs, two garden lawn chairs), undated (Box 253)
        PF# 0098a
      - Cyclists (Bill Burns, left and Tom Burns, right), 1983 (Box 253)
        PF# 0099c
      - Woman and Arbor Vitae, 1980 (Box 253)
        PF# 0100c
      - (seven people playing and working outside), undated (Box 253)
        PF# 0101c
      - Hanna Brenken and Ricardo Weisenberg -artists, undated (Box 253)
        PF# 0102d
      - (two men standing on wooden footbridge), undated (Box 253)
        PF# 0103d
      - Man with a Landscape Painting (John Haigney-artist-showed with RG), 1980 (Box 253)
        PF# 0104a
      - Woman with Flamingo Painting (Connie Evans-artist), 1982 (Box 253)
        PF# 0105c
      - Sisters and Babies, 1983 (Box 253)
        PF# 0106c
      - Hanna Brenken (seated) and Ricardo Weisenberg-artists, 1983 (Box 253)
        PF# 0107c
      - Adelaide Haigney (Box 253)
        PF# 0108c
      - Autumn Portrait (Bill Burns), 1984 (Box 254)
        PF# 0109d
      - Dancer (Victoria Burns), 1984 (Box 254)
        PF# 0110b
      - Woman on a Sofa, 1982 (Box 254)
        PF# 0111b
      - Woman with Snowball Bush (photographer Sandra Weiner, wife of Dan), 1983 (Box 254)
        PF# 0112b
      - Woman with Puppets, 1982 (Box 254)
        PF# 0113e
      - Woman with Hackberry Tree, 1983 (Box 254)
        PF# 0114c
      - Woman Under a Flowering Tree (Ann Ryden), 1987 (Box 254)
        PF# 0115c
      - Wedding Portrait (Tom and Victoria Burns), 1985 (Box 254)
        PF# 0116c
      - Val Telberg (photographer) and unidentified woman, 1985 (Box 254)
        PF# 0117d
      - Man with a Tray (Charles Phillips), 1984 (Box 254)
        PF# 0118b
      - Dog and Tree (a.k.a. Dog and Bush - dog's name is Bodo), 1982 (Box 254)
        PF# 0119c
      - Cat in a Driveway, 1979 (Box 254)
        PF# 0120d
      - Toba Tucker (photographer), 1984 (Box 254)
        PF# 0121c
      - Dog with a Covered Berry Bush, 1985 (Box 254)
        PF# 0122c
      - (seated dog and covered berry bush), 1985 (Box 254)
        PF# 0123
      - (seated man with electronic equipment), undated (Box 254)
        PF# 0124d
      - (man pinning laundry on line), undated (Box 254)
        PF# 0125d
      - (man with surveying equipment), 1979 (Box 254)
        PF# 0126d
      - (construction worker behind plastic sheeting), 1983 (Box 254)
        PF# 0127c
      - (chimney sweep with ladder), 1981 (Box 254)
        PF# 0128d
      - (man in thicket), undated (Box 255)
        PF# 0129c
      - (man standing on chair trimming branches), undated (Box 255)
        PF# 0130d
      - (girl hanging upside down on playground equipment), undated (Box 255)
        PF# 0131c
      - Woman Chopping Wood, 1986 (Box 255)
        PF# 0132d
      - Runner (Jonathan Silin), 1983 (Box 255)
        PF# 0133b
      - Couple With Pets (Charles [a.k.a. Chuck] Hitchcock and David Wilt), 1982 (Box 255)
        PF# 0134b
      - Fiddlers (Bill King-sculptor and Connie Fox, painter), 1985 (Box 255)
        PF# 0135d
      - Bill King (sculptor) and Connie Fox (painter) (both playing fiddle), 1985 (Box 255)
        PF# 0136
      - Young Woman with Doll's House (Lisa Vahradian-opera singer-see P0062), 1981 (Box 255)
        PF# 0137e
      - Portrait: Late Summer), 1986 (Box 255)
        PF# 0138c
      - The Palm Reading, 1984 (Box 255)
        PF# 0139a
      - (palm reading-variant of 0139a), 1984 (Box 255)
        PF# 0140d
      - (couple in backyard with child), undated (Box 255)
        PF# 0141d
      - Two Men Dancing (James Haigney and John Haigney), 1985 (Box 255)
        PF# 0142c
      - (backyard haircut - George Mitchell and Bill Burns), undated (Box 255)
        PF# 0143b
      - Child with Her Head in a Towel (a.k.a. Child in a Towel-Daisey Klingman), 1980 (Box 255)
        PF# 0144b
    - Nudes
      - Male
        - (male nude wearing angel wings, curtains), undated (Box 255)
          N# 0001a
        - (man seated on bed in robe and slippers-David Stein), undated (Box 255)
          N# 0002a
        - (male nude on zebra skin, vertical position), circa 1981 (Box 255)
          N# 0003
        - (male nude on zebra skin, diagonal position), 1981 (Box 255)
          N# 0004a
        - (Jonathan Silin, Amagansett), 1980 (Box 255)
          N# 0005a
        - (man seated on bed wearing leather harness), undated (Box 256)
          N# 0006a
          See 0002a
        - (male nude reclining on sofa bathed in sunlight), undated (Box 256)
          N# 0007b
        - (male nude, profile portrait), undated (Box 256)
          N# 0008b
        - Man Behind a Screen Door, 1986 (Box 256)
          N# 0009a
        - Mitchell and Lidell, 1983 (Box 256)
          N# 0010
        - (male nude leaning against wooden pedestal), 1989 (Box 256)
          N# 0011a
        - Man in Profile (Vincent Contrastano), 1981 (Box 256)
          N# 0012b
        - (two male nudes, plants, fence), undated (Box 256)
          N# 0013a
        - (two males nudes leaning against Philco radio), undated (Box 256)
          N# 0014a
        - Sunday Morning, 1989 (Box 256)
          N# 0015b
        - (two males nudes, one against tree, one in background), undated (Box 256)
          N# 0016
        - (two males nudes nestled on sofa), undated (Box 256)
          N# 0017b
        - (male nude on ground, black cat in background), undated (Box 256)
          N# 0018a
        - (male nude posed with bird feeder), undated (Box 256)
          N# 0019a
        - (male nude, back view, on deck bench), 1982 (Box 256)
          N# 0020a
        - Arthur Tress as the Muse of Photography, 1978 (Box 256)
          N# 0021d
        - (male nude perched on wooden post), undated (Box 256)
          N# 0022a
        - Man with a Towel (probably George Stambolian), 1982 (Box 256)
          N# 0023b
        - Man Exercising (Jonathan Silin), 1978 (Box 256)
          N# 0024
        - (Michael Lynch, writer-nude, hand on wall, sunlight, skimmer), undated (Box 256)
          N# 0025
        - (Michael Lynch, writer-nude in corner, sunlight, skimmer), 1984 (Box 257)
          N# 0026
        - (Michael Lynch, writer-male nude, sunlight), undated (Box 257)
          N# 0027a
        - (male nude posed against painted brick wall), undated (Box 257)
          N# 0028a
        - (Jonathan Silin, nude leaning on bicycle), 1975 (Box 257)
          N# 0029d
        - (male nude from rear, head turned), undated (Box 257)
          N# 0030b
        - Man Holding a Bar (John Albano), 1979 (Box 257)
          N# 0031b
        - (George Stambolian posed with projection of classic drawing), undated (Box 257)
          N# 0032a
        - (male nude, rear view, arms raised, arrows on wall), undated (Box 257)
          N# 0033a
        - (male nude, arms crossed, arrows on wall), undated (Box 257)
          N# 0034a
        - (male nude leaning on louvered door), 1979 (Box 257)
          N# 0035a
        - (male nude seated on sofa wearing one sock-Kevin), undated (Box 257)
          N# 0036a
        - (male nude propped in corner of bed), undated (Box 257)
          N# 0037a
        - (standing male nude, "Irene Chinese" sign), undated (Box 257)
          N# 0038a
        - (male nude with Evian, chairs hanging from ceiling), undated (Box 257)
          N# 0039a
        - (male nude posed with chair), undated (Box 257)
          N# 0040a
        - (reclining male nude with two cats), undated (Box 257)
          N# 0041a
        - (reclining male nude with one cat), undated (Box 257)
          N# 0042b
        - (male nude against marble pillar-writer George Grumley), undated (Box 257)
          N# 0043a
        - Man at Sink (Jonathan Silin), 1979 (Box 257)
          N# 0044a
        - Darryl: Standing (Darryl Yates Rist, journalist), 1986 (Box 257)
          N# 0045b
        - (Darryl Yates Rist, journalist-nude, rear view, head down), 1986 (Box 258)
          N# 0046b
        - (Darryl Yates Rist, journalist-nude, rear view, head vertical), 1986 (Box 258)
          N# 0047a
        - (George Stambolian, writer-seated on bed, arms around knees), 1984 (Box 258)
          N# 0048a
        - Man on a Motorcycle, 1977 (Box 258)
          N# 0050b
        - (male nude posed with black plastic), undated (Box 258)
          N# 0051a
        - (male nude posed on bed, sailor figuring on wall), undated (Box 258)
          N# 0052a
        - (male nude seated on bed, peering out window), undated (Box 258)
          N# 0053a
        - (male nude reclining on bed, star on wall), undated (Box 258)
          N# 0054a
        - (male nude seated in corner, broom at right), undated (Box 258)
          N# 0055a
        - (male nude standing in corner with broom), undated (Box 258)
          N# 0056a
        - (male nude, rear view, stepping into hot tub), undated (Box 258)
          N# 0057a
        - (male nude seated on edge of carpet), undated (Box 258)
          N# 0058a
        - (male nude seated in sunlight), undated (Box 258)
          N# 0059a
        - (seated male nude posed in cap), undated (Box 258)
          N# 0060a
        - (male nude with towel in bathtub, rear view), 1978 (Box 258)
          N# 0061
        - Man in His Shower, 1978 (Box 258)
          N# 0062
        - (male nude in bathtub, holding towel at left), 1978 (Box 258)
          N# 0063b
        - (crouching male nude, column), undated (Box 258)
          N# 0064a
        - (male nude leaning against bird cage), 1982 (Box 258)
          N# 0065a
        - (reclining male nude torso, horizontal-Jonathan Silin), undated (Box 258)
          N# 0066
        - (reclining male nude torso, diagonal-Jonathan Silin), undated (Box 259)
          N# 0067
        - (reclining male nude torso, hand on stomach-Jonathan Silin), undated (Box 259)
          N# 0068
        - (reclining male nude torso, reverse of 0067-Jonathan Silin), undated (Box 259)
          N# 0069
        - Man with a Mirror, 1979 (Box 259)
          N# 0070a
        - (two male nudes on sofa, one covered by blanket), undated (Box 259)
          N# 0071a
        - (male nude in corner, rear view, electrical cord on floor), 1984 (Box 259)
          N# 0074b
        - (male nude in corner, rear view, arms over head), 1984 (Box 259)
          N# 0075a
        - (male nude standing in corner, broom at left), undated (Box 259)
          N# 0076a
      - Female
        - (female nude, hands on hip, wearing skirt), undated (Box 259)
          N# 0077
        - (female nude, wearing skirt and net gloves), undated (Box 259)
          N# 0078
        - (female nude, between bench and window-Nadja Tassich [sp?], writer), 1984 (Box 259)
          N# 0079a
        - Woman with an Easel-Jane Kogan, artist, 1980 (Box 259)
          N# 0080c
        - (female nude with drum set-Connie Evans, artist), 1981 (Box 259)
          N# 0081b
        - (female nude on sofa, arm behind head-Jane Culver, photographer), 1986 (Box 259)
          N# 0082b
        - (female nude reclining on sofa, full figure-Jane Culver, photographer), 1986 (Box 259)
          N# 0083a
        - (Lisa Cresson in black skirt and gloves, holding black cat aloft), undated (Box 259)
          N# 0084a
        - (Lisa Cresson in black skirt and gloves, holding black cat in arms), undated (Box 259)
          N# 0085a
        - (pregnant nude posed with hat boxes, painting, etc.-Victoria Burns), undated (Box 259)
          N# 0086a
        - Woman with Jewelry-Muriel Dimen, writer, feminist psychoanalyst, 1981 (Box 259)
          N# 0087a
        - (female nude in yard with insect sculptures), undated (Box 259)
          N# 0088a
        - Model and Figure Painting, 1981 (Box 260)
          N# 0089b
      - With Figurative Elements
        - Man with Marilyn Calendar (Tom Burns), 1980 (Box 260)
          N# 0090c
        - Couple with Family Group (Lisa Cresson and Paul), 1987 (Box 260)
          N# 0091a
        - Man with a Plaster Torso, 1983 (Box 260)
          N# 0092b
        - (male nude holding open fan in front of face), 1979 (Box 260)
          N# 0093a
        - (male nude posed on carousel horse), undated (Box 260)
          N# 0094a
        - Man with a Marionette, 1978 (Box 260)
          N# 0095a
        - (male nude, face down on bed, hand on robot toy), 1989 (Box 260)
          N# 0096a
        - (male nude on bed with towel), 1989 (Box 260)
          N# 0097a
        - (male nude, crouching, cat), undated (Box 260)
          N# 0098a
        - Man with Nude Drawing, 1981 (Box 260)